Caught Up
压制:随Feng
Usher-Caught Up
Usher-对她着迷
I'm the kind of brotha
我是这样的人
Who been doin'it my way
以我的方式行事
Gettin' my bread for years
多年靠我的职业养活自己
In my career And every lover In and out my life
每一个走进走出我生活的情人
I hear love and left the tears
我听到爱的心声 留下了眼泪
Without a care
但没有真正在乎过
Until I met this girl who turned the tables around
直到我遇到这个女孩 她扭转了局面
She caught me by surprise
她让我惊讶
I never thought I'd be the one breaking down
我从没想过我会被打败
I cant figure it out why
我不能理解为什么我会这样
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Got me feelin' it
让我感受它
Caught up
对她着迷
I don't know what it is
我不知道这是什么
But it seems shes got me twisted
但她让我疯狂
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Got me feelin' it
让我感受它
Caught up
对她着迷
I'm losin' control
我失去了控制
This girls got a hold on me
这个女孩抓住了我的心
Let me go baby
让我走 宝贝
Now listen
听着
My momma told me
我妈妈告诉我
Be careful who you do cuz karma comes back around
小心你对别人做的 因为因果命运在你左右
Same ol' song
同样的老调调
But I was so sure
但我十分确定
That it wouldnt happen to me
这不会发生在我的身上
Cuz I know how to put it down
因为我知道如何把它放下
But I was so wrong
但是我错了
This girl was mean
这个女孩很难驾驭
She really turned me out
她向我证明了
Her body was so tight
她的身体如此的紧
I'm lookin' for her in the daytime with a flashlight
白天我带着闪光灯到处寻找她
My homies say this girl is crampin' my style
我的家人说这个女孩约束住了我的风格
And I can't figure it out but
我不理解
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Got me feelin' it
让我感受它
Caught up
对她着迷
I don't know what it is
我不知道这是什么
But it seems shes got me twisted
但她让我疯狂
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Got me feelin' it
让我感受它
Caught up
对她着迷
I'm losin' control
我失去了控制
This girls got a hold
这个女孩抓住了我的心
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Really feelin' it
让我感受它
Caught up
对她着迷
I don't know what it is
我不知道这是什么
But it seems shes got me twisted
但她让我疯狂
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Really feelin' it
让我感受它
Caught up
对她着迷
I'm losin' control
我失去了控制
This girls got a hold on me
这个女孩抓住了我的心
And I think I like it baby
我想我喜欢它 宝贝
Oh nooo, oh no
噢不 噢不
Ooh, yeaah, oh my
This girl was mean
这个女孩很难驾驭
She really turned me out
她向我证明了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, suga
My homies say this girl is crampin' my style
我的家人说这个女孩正在约束了我的风格
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Caught up
对她着迷
Don't know what it is
我不知道这是什么
But it seems shes got me twisted
但她让我疯狂
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Really feelin' it
真的感觉得到
Caught up
对她着迷
I'm losin' control
我失去了控制
This girls got a hold
这个女孩抓住了我
I'm so Caught up
我如此入迷
Im so Caught up
I don't know what it is
我不知道这是什么
But it seems shes got me twisted
但她让我疯狂
I'm Caught up
我如此入迷
Really feelin' it
真的感觉得到
Caught up
对她着迷
I'm losin' control
我失去了控制
This girls got a hold on me
这个女孩抓住了我的心
压制:随Feng